[Music]
Jeff you recently did a podcast for the
daily Evolver about Jordan Peterson and
I was really struck by of all of the
critiques that I've seen and I've done a
couple of documentaries about Peterson
now so I've been sort of studying the
phenomenon fairly fairly closely and a
lot of the critiques that I've seen have
come from quite a they seem a little bit
unfair or a little bit shrill or a bit
reactive and I wondered a couple of
things and your critique actually seemed
very very generous it seemed to be
coming from a place of yes and with
Peterson rather than a kind of objection
or or a feeling of reactivity towards
Peterson I wonder I've got a couple of
questions what one is why do you think
he creates that kind of reactivity and
why did your critique not have that
reactivity well I think he creates that
kind of reactivity because most people
are mano perspectival and you know just
to put a little bit of integral theory
on the table there's basically three
worldviews that are online in the
developed world right now that are in
contention the traditionalist worldview
which is you know more ethnocentric
religious conservative so forth the
modernist worldview which is secular and
sort of the business people the academic
whatever and the postmodern which is
more civil rights and you know
rehabilitating the people who have been
left behind and sensitivity and all of
that sort of thing so these are every
one of them thinks that they're right
and every one of them is at this stage
of that game because we have just in
terms of the development of cultures and
I'm talking in the developed world we've
polarized so we really know which side
of the street we're on you know so you
have a guy like Jordan Peterson come
along and he's actually has a facility
at all of these stages and
you know nobody knows where to put him
and so if he has a conservative of you
or if he comes where he's from where
he's defending religion or traditional
sex roles or things like you know
self-discipline and humility and then
people think he's in that box of the you
know crazy religious conservative and
you know the were you know were were
often running so that so to appreciate
Jordan Peterson you also have to be
somewhat mano perspectival and when I
talked about there being three stages
online traditional modern and postmodern
we would also posit this is the integral
thing that there's a next stage online
called integral which is an integration
of the best of what all of the three
previous stages have to offer okay so it
has the capacity to hold all three of
those stages and Jordan Peterson has
that capacity and that's why he's hit
such a nerve and and and and has been so
thrilling and also in terms of where he
well
maybe I'll stop there and and see would
you would you cite from the old
perspective he is an integral thinker
yes I would he is able to definitely
think integrally he has integral
cognition as we would say his his heart
in a way is in traditionalism in my
opinion in a way that I think keeps him
a little stuck there honestly but I
don't care because what he's doing is he
is helping this whole strata of people
who have never had traditionalism well
installed okay maybe they had postmodern
parents maybe they had read pre-modern
parents maybe they don't have any
parents but they didn't get the the
strata of tradition
which is where you're taught to sit down
and shut up where you have to be
obedient where you think that they're
theirs you see the sort of higher
natural hierarchies at least where
you're taught to be proud of your
country to have humility all of that
stuff and I guess the deepest story of
that is that your culture has value that
their solution airy story that has been
played out through through your culture
that you don't fully understand you
should have some kind of respect for
that absolutely absolutely
yes and that's the part that's
ethnocentric but and and really
difficult to for people who are at the
postmodern stage to have any
appreciation for that they just see it
as racist but so that's the integral
move is to see what is it about
Britishness what is it about persian as'
chineseness Americanist what is it
that's so precious you could just feel
it ringing through the land you know
that's that's important we want to bring
that online and and you've got to get
through green to do that you got to get
through post modernity to do that that
ain't easy just some some an interesting
tension that kind of you talked about on
your podcasts is that you know Peterson
has been asked a few times and I think
Jonathan rouse and also kind of asked
him around is okay so what elements of
post-modernism do we take forward and
his response was was sort of kind of
none this is pretty much ideological
possession I find that a very
interesting point because I think from a
lot of my kind of progressive or green
friends they that's the main sticking
point with them
I think it's that no but they're and I
would agree to you know to a degree
where it's like yeah there are some very
valuable things to take through so what
are your thoughts on his kind of stance
on that of like no you you throw it you
throw that baby out with the bathwater
yeah I think that's the part that is the
the real sticking part of him really
moving into a
integral embrace you know a real you
know where where his hearts more at the
integral stage instead of just his head
yeah he sees I think you know maybe he
has been as a lot of us have been who
have been in graduate school recently
you know sort of traumatized by the
whole thing especially if you're a white
guy you know that there is a there's
absolutely a new kind of hierarchy where
the victim is on top and you know that
and that's just as oppressive there's a
lot of what we would say in the red or
pre-modern sort of warrior the fighting
stance that is that green is infected
with you know and all of that's true and
and I'm glad that Jordan Peterson is
fighting that battle but when he talks
about you know sensitivity who he
refuses to talk to anybody who would
talk about white privilege you know
that's that's sort of ideological if you
ask me and in in in and so he sees that
whole sort of move towards sensitivity
that and femininity I also think that he
there's a lot of unnecessary sort of
sorting out of masculine and feminine
qualities to men and women you know in a
way that feels that the perfect world
for Jordan Peterson would be some sort
of a better more improved stage right at
the traditional and modern stage of
development you know a really good
version of that would be his perfect
world and that's you know I think that
actually you know gender fluidity and a
lot of these things are actually
harbingers of what's to come you know
and in the people go overboard with it
yeah join the club this is humanity we
always do but we're also staking out new
territory that will allow ultimately
the full range of human capacities from
the masculine pole to the feminine pole
and there they're those masculine and
feminine poles are there and they're
juicy and we want to we don't want to
blend them we don't want homogenized
them which is what post modernity tries
to do so we see that they're separate
but we also say that they're they're
available to everybody regardless of
biological sex now people we're going to
sort out the way they sort out and
people are going to have what
preferences they have but the the whole
landscape is available when we talk
about post-modernism there's there's a
lot of terms that seem that they could
get kind of conflated here because
Peterson certainly has a real dislike of
certain aspects of post modernity and
Wilber also talks about this idea of the
eighth a perspective or madness that
hidden within post-modernism is a is a
worldview that doesn't really make any
sense
I guess Peterson would call it it's not
a playable game to the idea that
everything is equally valid and nothing
is true is not something that you can
actually live out in your life so it's
and I wonder when when some integral
thinkers in particular sort of say well
Peterson is is very anti green they seem
like his real vitriol seems to be aimed
at least from my perspective towards
that that a perspective or madness the
idea that there are no truths rather
than the things that have come out of
Greenwich you might talk of civil rights
and yeah that the the kind of the green
civil rights wave right yeah the
positive the unqualified positive of
green of post modernity no it's true and
I think he does really focus on that you
know a perspectival madness the idea
that there is no truth and he points out
that where that leads and this is again
another sort of developmental thing
mistake or that I would add this to the
mix is that in 2018
world this is not going to lead to the
gulag okay so you know he gets all
worked up about where this sort of a
perspectival thing can lead and points
out the you know the history of the 20th
century well part of the history of the
20th century is that we have at least in
the developed world about the whole
world actually but in the developed
world we've moved to a center of gravity
of modernity where you know it's just
we're pacified you know that that's not
a real threat anymore and I just would
you know point that out and you know and
I think that's another small critique
that I would happen but it's it's part
of what makes you know I think one of
the moves of integral is that we can
fight the same battles that we fought
all along but we do it without
demonizing our opponents and we do it
without hating them and we do it with a
certain love in lightness to our heart
that I don't quite recognize in Jordan
Peterson
yeah I think this is this is a really
good point because when he talks about
that there is this this worldview that
has so many people he talks about the
kind of the value of ideas and the post
modernity is a pernicious ideology and
it has people in their grip you would
imagine that the the logical next step
would be to have some empathy for these
people yes like if people have been
given ideas that are not their own and
they're following ideas that are not
their own surely that the thing to do is
to hold our hands out and say have some
empathy for the fact that they've been
misled rather than this this this really
strong attack on them which I get a lot
of time from Peterson yeah I think
that's that's valid and well said and
and also to appreciate the the actual
positive
of nature of that radical deconstruction
you know part of what that's all about
is deconstructing these grand narratives
of history whether it's the you know
everything's going to be great once
everybody accepts Jesus as their
personal Savior okay so that's the grant
narrative traditionalists of modernists
everything's going to be great once
everybody becomes rational okay that
proves to be wrong you know so post
modernity comes in and says okay
all of your grand narratives you know
all of your tribe will all of your
religion all of your ideas of truth and
there is something that is just
necessary about that cleansing even
though it leaves you nuts and depressed
and useless there is that hiss of stage
on the path that you want to get through
as quickly as possible and a lot of
people are stuck there but there is
something beyond that and so that brings
on a respect for that in a way that I
don't get from Peterson it's an
interesting thing because Francois
Lyotard one of the kind of fathers of
post-modernism said at one point that
all this deconstruction if it's not
tempered by the sublime this point where
there is absolute meaning which is
almost like your North Star if you have
that point the deconstruction could be
incredibly productive it's enough for me
from my background it's a psychedelic
kind of experience you know everything
that wall certain becomes relational etc
but he made a point of that very early
on in this intellectual endeavor to say
without the sublime the postmodern will
lead to madness and I thought what's
interesting for me watching Peterson is
a big part of what he's reviving is the
sublime in some sense through the
unconscious
Christianity yes indeed he is and and I
love he's a beautiful transmitter of the
sublime beautiful transmitter I mean
I've seen things that have given me
chills when he talks about whether or
not you make your bed has cosmic
consequences I agree actually and and to
actually get that's cosmos centric you
know we talked about moving from
ethnocentric to world centric you know
to cosmos centric in an integral week
where we start you know getting in touch
with the actual animating energetics of
the cosmos you know and there's a new
rien chant minh the world that comes
online at that point because we actually
do realize that there's a new creation
story that is you know delivered to us
by science it's not we don't have to
bypass science science shows us that
something came out of nothing 13.8
billion years ago and as complexified
into us now there's a spiritual path in
there somewhere and we don't have to get
you know all stuck I mean we could see
the our religious traditions our you
know pre-modern or Christianity all of
them as beautiful you know art forms
spiritual art forms full of beautiful
practices for this realization that we
are evolving creatures in an evolving
cosmos and we've come from somewhere
we're going from somewhere and the you
know for me the only way any of it makes
sense is if there is some continuity
between lifetimes you know you don't
have to believe that but I'm not sure I
believe that but you know I you could
play with that because we could actually
see it it's science shows it to us my
just sort of going back a little bit to
the idea of post modernity is sort of
this cleansing and then we reconstruct
afterwards I I hear a lot of people
talking talking like that in terms of
the that's the process we're going
through but I guess what I really got an
appreciation of listening to Peterson is
there are some things we cannot erase
that there is a biological lived reality
there are certain archetypal structures
that are just pre-existing because of
the way that that we exist as biological
creatures the
that actually post modernity cannot
erase and that this is something that
I'm sort of struggling with a little bit
because yeah there's that there's a this
what post modernity does it erase it
thinks it does yeah that's that's that's
a distinction I would make you know an
integral rewear I realize what you're
saying is true is that wait a wait a
minute no there are things that are
actually true that you know the you know
boiling point of water that the the the
you know whatever is there is there are
actual true things and so that we sort
of you know correct for the excesses of
you know extreme deconstruction yeah and
that I think Peterson's phrase was that
our experience of the world is
parameterised by a biological heritage
and by our embodied nature and that's
something as well I mean I mentioned it
before the idea of a playable game is a
really clever idea it's like yeah you
can say you can you can play the
postmodern game as much as you want but
and say that all all possibilities are
equally valid okay go and try and live
that out in your life and see what
happens exactly you know that's why you
know that that philosophy or that
worldview exists in academia because you
actually don't have to go out and do
anything but but you know talk about it
in the real world people are disabused
of that pretty quickly you know I mean
yeah III get the problem and you know I
think that Peterson is doing God's work
and in you know confronting that as
beautifully as he is yeah and for me I
mean I've done quite a lot of kind of
inner work and been part of I guess
spiritual communities for quite a long
time and what I really got from Peterson
was a real sense of the kind of
reinvention of the Christian tradition
and
to post Christianity that integrates
this incredible intellectual and
spiritual tradition in a way that makes
intelligible to me and so I'm sure to
many other people I mean I was raised a
Christian and then I started reading ein
Rand and then I went into atheism you
know then I moved to Boulder and you
know I became all postmodern but but
part of my continued growth is turning
and reom bracing the the spiritual
truths of Christianity you know that are
given to us through Christianity and no
other place you know that I'd say the
same for Buddhism that's the other
religion I've deeply practiced and I
can't imagine my life without both God
and emptiness but you you know you can't
get a Christian or a Buddhist that you
know go to the other Pole but I love
both of those poles I love both of those
things and I feel seen and loved by God
in a way that I never imagined in my
early 20s that I would you know and I'm
so glad that Jordan Peterson is you know
reach an ting this you know disenchanted
world of modernity for people honor God
I mean yeah we are we're you know no
free will and you know just accidents
what matter I mean I don't know it's
it's it's very depressing very distant
heart disheartening for people and so
he's again literally doing God's work
yeah I think by my friend Andrew Sweeney
said he's one of the few people in the
world that seems to be on fire with the
holy spirit which is a yeah it's it's so
true there is something very yeah yeah
I've said it before he has a very
performative aspect to what he's doing
but when you look at his philosophy
seems very aligned with it he talks
about the logos and the idea that you
incarnate the logos more in your own lie
and by doing so you become more embodied
you become more present and and he is a
living example of that which is
something I'd never put those two things
together before quite so clearly and as
when I was listening to him ah yeah
beautiful yeah it's a it's actually it's
interesting if you look at postmodern
art compared to art that really follows
the kind of Union monomyth so if you
look at like Waiting for Godot where
there's just two guys waiting for you
know you know metaphor for God and
nothing happens you know that was my was
through I studied English literature it
was through stuff that was really crappy
to read you know and what Peterson is
doing is kind of moving away from that
as a I think a cultural reference point
to know it's Lord of the Rings and
you're Frodo you know it's it's that
kind of mythic journey and I think to a
degree that's perhaps why it appeals to
men and young men in particular who feel
directionless that'd be an interesting
thing to get your perspective on of this
disappear to the masculine that Peterson
house oh yes no it's beautiful and and
it's a palliative to a world
particularly in academia in certain
aspects of the culture that have become
you know feminized in a way that's you
know pernicious too much and so you know
this whole group of young men feel yeah
there's no meaning there's this there's
no religion that you know you know a
toxic masculinity you know I have all
this privilege it sure as hell doesn't
feel like it but I guess I do no no no
we're here you know we're here
this precious human life I mean good god
we're the creations of Almighty God
somehow here we are and we're here for a
reason and one of the things that you
know we want to bring forward into
integral into an integral sensibility is
what we left behind when we moved into
modernity which is
world that is dripping with meaning you
know where everything matters you know
who you meet who you talk to whether or
not you made your bed what thoughts
you're thinking you know that's all part
of this heroic journey and every person
you meet is the little Frodo or a little
somebody who has something for you you
know you can sort of have that as a
practice to say what does that person
have for me why do I have for them you
know as I move through this amazing
journey that you know it's tragic it's
kamek it's you know all of humanity what
the are we doing here I mean this
is really yeah this is absolutely
fascinating this was something that came
to me on the plane
on the way over to interview Peterson
was I made a few documentaries about
Isis and I've always felt what a
seductive worldview that is to go from
being I don't know someone kind of
working in a shop somewhere to on the
front lines of the struggle for your
civilization and then it struck me that
what Peterson is doing through the the
wider mythological work and framing it
within this kind of theological
framework is making your life as
meaningful as that that every single
thing you do is taking the world either
closer to or further away from hell and
it's it's essential it seems to me
absolutely essential if we're going to
kind of struggle against those kind of
very seductive worldviews but we need
something like this yes yes no it's so
true and and you know God might have
caused my centric as well yes absolutely
yeah and we could see it in play you
know I mean something came out of
nothing and it's us you know good lord
but yeah it's you know the the we we
want to you know we talked about the
three big stages that are online
there's actually three stages that we
identify that are previous to that and
those are the worlds of like tribal
magic and in great myths and we went
those back on
- you know we want to see that the world
you know that nature is enchanted and I
love that about Jordan Peterson he has
this sort of Native American practice
that he does with this sort of community
that I think is really helps round out
the guy you had on the end of your
documentary David did the guide Road in
Greenville yes my goodness gracious what
a integral transmission about you know
taking it back down to zero and nature
and communication and contact with other
human beings and yes yes yes yes that is
that that's where we're going and that's
where modernity gets stuck because
modernity you know has to get rid of all
of the superstition and all of the magic
all of the myth that's its job it
reduces everything to the exterior z-- -
what's measurable it has notes you know
use for meaning or any of that kind of
stuff and so for a lot of people they
think that the only way to greet to
reach aunt my life or to enchant my life
is to go back to some sort of a mythic
religion and and then a lot of people
can't do that you know you just can't
uncook that egg you know what I mean and
so a lot of people who are have a modern
sensibility can't go back to a mythic
meaning-making system and what they need
to know is that we can go forward to a
meaning making systems that Rhian chance
the world in a way that science not only
doesn't have a problem with it delivers
it to us it's so fascinated and I have
been talking recently about Terence
Mckenna
who is one of my favorite thinkers and
you know he he had a book called the
archaic revival and that really you know
it's it's that idea really it's that
kind of reinterment and is taking the
archaic but not going back but saying
yes and I think you're braiding it into
it's it's so essential yeah yeah right
on yeah and you know I think Jordan
Peterson is doing his part you know in a
way that looks like a Sam Harris another
hero of mine in a way
you know steven pinker another hero of
mine Jonathan Hite another you know
there's some great public intellectuals
I have critiques of all of them in a
certain way but one of the things that
Jordan Peterson is bringing to the party
is you know a certain kind of magic you
know immediate meaning yeah he he is
telling but for me at least my my
feeling of even when I first encountered
his thought is that he is telling that
the deep story of Western culture better
than anyone I've ever seen yes and doing
it from a very deeply embodied place and
this is I mean I found I guess I found
out about him last July last June or
July and then immediately kind of went
over and interviewed him fairly soon
afterwards and I was convinced I knew as
soon as I found him this was the right
voice for the times that he was and
nothing that's happened since in terms
of his kind of rocketing to fame has
surprised me in any any way whatsoever
it was so clear that this was an
essential voice for right now and and is
kind of you could look at it slightly
scary as well it's like we've lost sight
of things to this point that we are so
thirsty for it that we need this kind of
transmission right now and I think it's
a sign of how far we've strayed from
these eternal truths that that he has
become so famous in such a short amount
of time yeah I mean the only thing I
would say is I agree with all of that I
would just say that the strain also was
fruitful and that you know you know
there's there's there's something about
that you know what are the markers of
the postmodern view particularly is
people are depressed you know we're
living in this ever darkening world and
you know that that one of the things I
loved about Jordan Peterson is he you
know there's a million of these little
youtubes and stuff but I don't pretend
to have seen them all but he did this
one on the beauty of high functioning
depression
that I thought was just fantastic you
know and and and it you know sort of if
it gives meaning to that and so you know
the the world the Lord works in
mysterious ways and we we you know it's
a messy progress process this I I often
say evolution is beautiful but not
pretty and you know you can look at
human history and you can see that yeah
so you know I I totally resonate with
that and you know if I look at my own
personal journey as an individual you
know you go through a long dark night of
the soul very often in a spiritual
journey and during it I you know you've
you're in that eight perspectival
madness
it's horrible after it for me I'm you
know my feeling is I would never change
that it made me who I am
so what elements of this journey we've
been on through post modernity do you
think we need to take into integral and
what do we need to leave behind well we
need to take it the integral of the
sensitivity of post modernity and of
green you know that sort of sensitivity
to all the people who've been left out
of the previous stages so we could say
that you know traditionalism tends to
divide the world between saints and
sinners post modernity says we went to
sinners you know modernity says winners
and losers post modernity says what we
went the losers to it so you know that
we want to have a you know equality you
know it it's it's over
you know they overdo it and it's you
know very Christian to me yes it is yes
this is my theory about this isn't
really interesting it's like from a lot
of kind of people talking about the
benefits of green it's like there's a
sort of idea that there was this this
wave of egalitarianism that came in in
the 60s and then we we had civil rights
we had gay rights we had women's
liberation I
I suspect and I don't know but I suspect
Peterson might say no that's not a new
thing that's come in that's actually the
natural consequence of the Christian
idea of the innate value and divinity of
every individual playing itself out on a
wider level and so you could actually
trace that down a lot further than a new
force that comes into play in the 60s
what do you got Eric fair enough I mean
I think that's I think that's a really
legitimate point for sure I mean Jesus
Jesus was Green you know but we could
also see the stages of a Christian of
the church you know and that the what
what we get a full blossoming of in post
modernity is that all of these all of
the human dignities are bestowed on
everybody not just my religion not just
my country not just my people my race
but everybody and particularly the
people who have been left behind but
you're right it is the full fruition of
the teachings of Jesus Christ absolutely
right but but for the first time yeah
it's it's yeah it's actually
it also shows up the hypocrisy of the
previous manifestation of some of these
you know how humans do it I mean we it's
it's amazing that you know people like
the great saints and sages like Christ
and Buddha the people who've really
magnetized people are actually teach to
have their teachings are from you know
post integral stages of development and
there's something about their teachings
and their transmission that is riveting
to the rest of us but we translate it
into our own stage of development and we
use it to gouge each other's eyes out
for you know few other few thousand
years until we finally really get it but
it is interesting how that works yeah I
think for me one of those most
interesting things of what we've already
covered is this reintroduction of the
transcendent
I think that's such a galvanizing pour I
think it's why Star Wars is popular
because got the force without the force
Star Wars would be just I don't think it
would doing well you know and I've often
thought about Peterson and that's the
revival that needs to happen but ya know
I mean
the force is definitely with him for the
moment yeah and you know may he you know
one of the things I would just say in a
favor of Jordan Peterson as you know
cutting edge you know even you know I
have my critiques about it whatever but
he has a flexibility of mind and a
resistance to being put in boxes and a
sense of I'm learning too you know and a
sense of provisional you know that
there's a humility yes yes thank you
that I think is remarkable considering
all his gifts and so you know I'm a fan
yeah I guess that would be my only
question is you've been quite sort of
clear on where you you see him falling
short or not his blind spots but you
still started off this conversation by
saying that you thought he was an
integral thinker yeah I mean in you know
this is part of the developmental schema
but you know we could we develop in
certain lines of development and and one
of we talked about is sort of the
leading line is cognition that is are we
actually able to see different systems
of thought so there's one thing to see
them and then there's another thing to
sort of install them in your sort of
heart and then there's another thing to
really get down into your belly you know
so I would say that you know I'm
integral from the waist up on a good day
you know I'd say George org Peterson is
integral from the neck up but a good day
I don't know who knows but that's what
I'm talking about yeah I also think that
he seems to have integrated or at least
to be able to access read in a way that
very few people in this culture are and
I think that's part of what gives him
the performative aspect like he he has
anger and the shadow at his at his call
in a way that for sure quite
intimidating as well for a lot of people
ya know I think you're right and that
and that also is a marker of integral is
somebody who can access read without
being you know just completely driven or
contained by read but when we talk about
read we're talking about just sure sheer
power you know the use of power and so
being willing to get into the arena
being willing to have conflict being
willing to cut somebody's head off being
willing to have your own head cut off
you know that kind of stuff that's
warrior today is a good day to die the
marker of that redness and we want to
have that you know and he does you're
right and that's one of the reasons that
he his followers are so passionate is
that they they want and this is
evolutionarily potent we what you know
we fight our way forward we also the
other F word our way forward but fight
our way forward to and and so you know
that he is a warrior it's one of the
things I talked about I am most admire
him in my podcast was that he's a
fighter and yeah that's that's you know
that's great I think that's a that's a
cool quality action because you know to
some degree the Trump and brexit
phenomena are a reaction against the
hypocrisy of green for not integrating
their red it's this kind of like you are
not as inclusive as you think you are
you've got that anger in you like we're
gonna go to you and troll you until you
show it like that's a really interesting
thing happening yeah I do too that's
well said yeah I guess that was a big
part of the the glitch in the matrix
documentary for me was this shadow of
liberalism this idea that liberalism is
there's a hypocrisy and liberalism
because
there is a tribalism we are naturally
tribal creatures and until we accept and
understand that you know we're
completely open we're completely
accepting we are so tolerant except for
those people who don't think like we do
[Laughter]
that's it yeah no it's true
we are the kind of creatures that don't
make sense so I'm glad you like the
glitch film as well yeah that's that's
what I was going to say actually is that
in terms of actual integral transmission
I thought the glitch in the matrix that
you did is as integral as anything I've
seen the people that you interviewed the
way you presented it it was I was
thrilled to see it and I'm really
interested in seeing you know more of
your stuff it's interesting that you say
that the glitch was an integral
transmission because at one point I want
we did actually record some integral
stuff that I was toying with putting in
and then he in the end didn't but it was
a real influence on the construction of
it and and was yeah a big sort of
invisible superstructure on what I was
putting together so it's interesting
that you spotted it yeah well if we're
right integral is not just you know a
theory it's the next stage of human
history unfolding and so people are
going to be thinking integrally whether
they have ever read a kid Wilbur book or
not and and we're seeing more and more
of that and I boy definitely saw it in
your your documentary yeah well really
great meeting you David and Allie great
meeting you as well yeah yes
Godspeed guys